{
    "questions":[
        {
            "Question": "I am ___ to the store.",
            "Correct": "walking",
            "Incorrect1": "walked",
            "Incorrect2": "walks",
            "Incorrect3": "walk"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He is ___ in the shower.",
            "Correct": "singing",
            "Incorrect1": "sing",
            "Incorrect2": "sings",
            "Incorrect3": "sang"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She is ___ breakfast.",
            "Correct": "eating",
            "Incorrect1": "eats",
            "Incorrect2": "eat",
            "Incorrect3": "ate"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We are ___ for the test.",
            "Correct": "studying",
            "Incorrect1": "studied",
            "Incorrect2": "studies",
            "Incorrect3": "study"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She ___ Spanish fluently.",
            "Correct": "speaks",
            "Incorrect1": "speak",
            "Incorrect2": "speaking",
            "Incorrect3": "speaked"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He has been ___ hard.",
            "Correct": "working",
            "Incorrect1": "works",
            "Incorrect2": "worked",
            "Incorrect3": "work"
        },
        {
            "Question": "They are ___ soon.",
            "Correct": "visiting",
            "Incorrect1": "visit",
            "Incorrect2": "visits",
            "Incorrect3": "visited"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He ___ in a bank.",
            "Correct": "works",
            "Incorrect1": "worker",
            "Incorrect2": "working",
            "Incorrect3": "work"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She ___ beautifully.",
            "Correct": "sings",
            "Incorrect1": "sung",
            "Incorrect2": "singing",
            "Incorrect3": "sing"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We are ___ to the beach.",
            "Correct": "biking",
            "Incorrect1": "bike",
            "Incorrect2": "bikes",
            "Incorrect3": "biked"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I am ___ to the store.",
            "Correct": "going",
            "Incorrect1": "go ",
            "Incorrect2": "goes",
            "Incorrect3": "went"
        },
        {
            "Question":"I ___ breakfast this morning.",
            "Correct": "ate",
            "Incorrect1": "eating",
            "Incorrect2": "eats",
            "Incorrect3": "eaten"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I am ___ on the computer.",
            "Correct": "typing",
            "Incorrect1": "typed",
            "Incorrect2": "types",
            "Incorrect3": "typer"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He is ___ a book.",
            "Correct": "reading",
            "Incorrect1": "read",
            "Incorrect2": "reads",
            "Incorrect3": "reader"
        },
        {
            "Question": "They ___ to the movies last night.",
            "Correct": "went",
            "Incorrect1": "going",
            "Incorrect2": "goes",
            "Incorrect3": "go"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We are ___ a movie.",
            "Correct": "watching",
            "Incorrect1": "watch",
            "Incorrect2": "watched",
            "Incorrect3": "watcher"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She will be ___ the party.",
            "Correct": "attending",
            "Incorrect1": "attend",
            "Incorrect2": "attends",
            "Incorrect3": "attended"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He had ___ in a bank.",
            "Correct": "worked",
            "Incorrect1": "work",
            "Incorrect2": "works",
            "Incorrect3": "working"
        },
        {
            "Question": "He was ___ on the phone.",
            "Correct": "talking",
            "Incorrect1": "talks",
            "Incorrect2": "talk",
            "Incorrect3": "talked"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We have ___ to the mall.",
            "Correct": "gone",
            "Incorrect1": "go",
            "Incorrect2": "went",
            "Incorrect3": "goes"
        },
        {
            "Question": "They had been ___ for hours.",
            "Correct": "waiting",
            "Incorrect1": "waits",
            "Incorrect2": "wait",
            "Incorrect3": "waited"
        },
        {
            "Question":"The cat ___ on the couch.",
            "Correct": "slept",
            "Incorrect1": "sleep ",
            "Incorrect2": "sleeping",
            "Incorrect3": "sleeper"
        },
        {
            "Question": "They are ___ catch.",
            "Correct": "playing",
            "Incorrect1": "plays",
            "Incorrect2": "play",
            "Incorrect3": "played"
        },
        {
            "Question":" I ___ a headache yesterday.",
            "Correct": "have",
            "Incorrect1": "has",
            "Incorrect2": "have been",
            "Incorrect3": "has been"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I had been ___ errands.",
            "Correct": "running",
            "Incorrect1": "runs",
            "Incorrect2": "ran",
            "Incorrect3": "run"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He has been ___ in the shower.",
            "Correct": "singing",
            "Incorrect1": "sing",
            "Incorrect2": "sings",
            "Incorrect3": "sang"
        },
        {
            "Question": "We are ___ in the backyard.",
            "Correct": "sitting",
            "Incorrect1": "sit",
            "Incorrect2": "sits",
            "Incorrect3": "sat"
        },
        {
            "Question":"The sky ___ blue yesterday.",
            "Correct": "was",
            "Incorrect1": "were",
            "Incorrect2": "are",
            "Incorrect3": "is"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She was ___ a nap.",
            "Correct": "taking",
            "Incorrect1": "take",
            "Incorrect2": "took",
            "Incorrect3": "takes"
        },
        {
            "Question":"You are ___ the birds.",
            "Correct": "feeding",
            "Incorrect1": "feed",
            "Incorrect2": "fed",
            "Incorrect3": "feeds"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I ___ to the store yesterday.",
            "Correct": "went",
            "Incorrect1": "go ",
            "Incorrect2": "goes",
            "Incorrect3": "gone"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He is ___ basketball.",
            "Correct": "playing",
            "Incorrect1": "plays",
            "Incorrect2": "play",
            "Incorrect3": "played"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She is ___ dinner.",
            "Correct": "making",
            "Incorrect1": "makes",
            "Incorrect2": "make",
            "Incorrect3": "made"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We are ___ in the choir.",
            "Correct": "singing",
            "Incorrect1": "sing",
            "Incorrect2": "sings",
            "Incorrect3": "sang"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She ___ beautifully at the concert.",
            "Correct": "sang",
            "Incorrect1": "singing",
            "Incorrect2": "sing",
            "Incorrect3": "sung"
        },
        {
            "Question":"You are ___ the grass.",
            "Correct": "cutting",
            "Incorrect1": "cut",
            "Incorrect2": "cuts",
            "Incorrect3": "cutter"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I am ___ the furniture.",
            "Correct": "dusting",
            "Incorrect1": "dust",
            "Incorrect2": "dusts",
            "Incorrect3": "dusted"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He is ___ rope.",
            "Correct": "skipping",
            "Incorrect1": "skips",
            "Incorrect2": "skip",
            "Incorrect3": "skipped"
        },
        {
            "Question": "We will be ___ next month.",
            "Correct": "travelling",
            "Incorrect1": "travel",
            "Incorrect2": "travels",
            "Incorrect3": "travelled"
        },
        {
            "Question":"They are ___ ice cream.",
            "Correct": "eating",
            "Incorrect1": "eat",
            "Incorrect2": "eats",
            "Incorrect3": "ate"
        },
        {
            "Question": "She had been ___ video games.",
            "Correct": "playing",
            "Incorrect1": "plays",
            "Incorrect2": "play",
            "Incorrect3": "played"
        },
        {
            "Question":"I am ___ TV.",
            "Correct": "watching",
            "Incorrect1": "watch",
            "Incorrect2": "warched",
            "Incorrect3": "watches"
        },
        {
            "Question": "He was ___ to work.",
            "Correct": "walking",
            "Incorrect1": "walks",
            "Incorrect2": "walked",
            "Incorrect3": "walk"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He is ___ breakfast.",
            "Correct": "making",
            "Incorrect1": "makes",
            "Incorrect2": "make",
            "Incorrect3": "made"
        },
        {
            "Question": " I have been ___ emails.",
            "Correct": "writing",
            "Incorrect1": "write",
            "Incorrect2": "writes",
            "Incorrect3": "wrote"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We are ___ rope.",
            "Correct": "jumping",
            "Incorrect1": "jump",
            "Incorrect2": "jumps",
            "Incorrect3": "jumped"
        },
        {
            "Question": "They are ___ the dog.",
            "Correct": "washing",
            "Incorrect1": "wash",
            "Incorrect2": "washes",
            "Incorrect3": "washed"
        },
        {
            "Question":"The book ___ on the table when I came in.",
            "Correct": "was",
            "Incorrect1": "were",
            "Incorrect2": "is",
            "Incorrect3": "are"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I am ___ the car.",
            "Correct": "fixing",
            "Incorrect1": "fix",
            "Incorrect2": "fixed",
            "Incorrect3": "fixes"
        },
        {
            "Question":"She will ___ Spanish fluently when she moves to Spain.",
            "Correct": "speak",
            "Incorrect1": "speaks",
            "Incorrect2": "speaking",
            "Incorrect3": "spoke"
        },
        {
            "Question": "He will ___ in a bank when he graduates.",
            "Correct": "work",
            "Incorrect1": "works",
            "Incorrect2": "works",
            "Incorrect3": "worked"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We have ___ to the park.",
            "Correct": "gone",
            "Incorrect1": "went",
            "Incorrect2": "goes",
            "Incorrect3": "go"
        },
        {
            "Question": "They will be ___ overnight.",
            "Correct": "staying",
            "Incorrect1": "stays",
            "Incorrect2": "stayed",
            "Incorrect3": "stay"
        },
        {
            "Question":"She has been ___ a blog.",
            "Correct": "writing",
            "Incorrect1": "write",
            "Incorrect2": "writes",
            "Incorrect3": "wrote"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I had been ___ for the exam.",
            "Correct": "studying",
            "Incorrect1": "study",
            "Incorrect2": "studies",
            "Incorrect3": "studied"
        },
        {
            "Question":"He will be ___ the meeting.",
            "Correct": "attending",
            "Incorrect1": "addend",
            "Incorrect2": "attends",
            "Incorrect3": "attend"
        },
        {
            "Question": "I will be ___ to the store later.",
            "Correct": "going",
            "Incorrect1": "go",
            "Incorrect2": "went",
            "Incorrect3": "goes"
        },
        {
            "Question":"We are ___ video games.",
            "Correct": "playing",
            "Incorrect1": "plays",
            "Incorrect2": "play",
            "Incorrect3": "played"
        },
        {
            "Question": "They are ___ the closet.",
            "Correct": "organizing",
            "Incorrect1": "organizes",
            "Incorrect2": "organize",
            "Incorrect3": "organized"
        },
        {
            "Question":"She will ___ beautifully at the wedding.",
            "Correct": "sing",
            "Incorrect1": "sang",
            "Incorrect2": "sings",
            "Incorrect3": "sung"
        }
        
    ] 
    
}
       
       